Alright, drink we're about to make is called Ponderosa.
Not only is a nice, classy restaurant with a fantastic salad bar, it's also a very good shot.
I'm going to server it up chilled, go ahead and put some ice in a glass.
And we'll measure out two ounces of grain alcohol, preferably a hundred and ninety proof.
There's one, and two.
And we'll follow that up with two ounces of orange soda.
And orange soda will do, since you're mixing it up with some super strong liquor, doesn't really matter on the quality there.
Alright, go ahead and just mix that back and forth a couple times, you don't want to, don't want to shake it up because of the carbonation in the soda.
Let's go ahead and grab a couple over sized shot glasses here, and get our strainer, and we'll pour it in.
Got a nice orange shot with a lot of alcohol that you're really not going to taste a whole lot.
Bottoms up.